pymetrics.com 2016-04-25

# Privacy Policy

Pymetrics is created by pymetrics Inc. (“pymetrics”, “Company”, “we”, “us” or “our”), we know your privacy is important to you and pymetrics is fully committed to your privacy.

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”, as more fully defined below) that we gather when you are accessing our Website, pymetrics.com (the “Site”) and/or when you download and install Pymetrics application for mobile devices (the “App”) . This policy does not apply to processes we do not control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.

BY USING THE SITE, YOU REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTOOD, AND AGREE TO THE TERMS OF, THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND OR DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY LEAVE THE SITE.

WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

We gather information which enables us to personalize and improve our services. We collect the following types of information from our customers.

Personal Information You Provide To Us:

In order for you to use certain of the Site’s Services, you may be asked to provide to us with certain Personal Information. Personal Information includes, without limitation: (1) “Contact Data” (such as your name, company name, mailing address, and e-mail address); (2) “Financial Data” (such as your account or credit card number); (3) “Demographic Data” (such as you zip code and age); and (4) “Auxiliary Data” (such as your level of education, work experience, leaderships and accomplishments, skills, short biography description, or picture). In each case, you will be asked to provide Personal Information; the Site or the App will not gather it surreptitiously. Company may supplement the Personal Information you provide with additional Personal Information gathered from public sources or from third-parties (e.g., consumer reporting agencies) who may lawfully provide such information to us.

You are under no obligation to provide Personal Information, with the caveat that your refusal to do so may prevent you from using certain of the Site’s or App’s Services.

Information Collected Automatically:

We may receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our Site, App or services. The Company automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser or mobile system including your IP address, Company cookie information, the page you requested and game, test and training program data.

Generally, our service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our site and its components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show. Company uses this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally.

What Are Cookies?

Like many websites, we use cookies and other standard web technology to collect information for our own use.

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our Site are visited and by how many people.

Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of our Web site’s most attractive features. If you disable the cookie feature, you assume all responsibility for any resulting loss of functionality on the Site.

HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We use information we collect to authenticate your visits and send you information and products.

If you have opted in to receiving marketing information, we use your personal information to customize and deliver that information to you.

We also use the information to manage and improve our Site, our App, our games, and our training. We may use your information, in aggregate form and in collaboration with outside researchers, to measure and quantify the effectiveness of our program. In our research, all the data is used in aggregate form or with your personal information removed. At no point will you be personally identifiable.

We may enhance or merge personal information with your other information and with data from third parties in order to better market and provide our products and services.

The Site and App may contain features, e.g. blogs, chat rooms, sharing functions, etc., that permit you to upload, post, transmit, display, perform or distribute content, information or other, including personal information. Any information that you choose to disclose by means of such features becomes public information over which we are unable to exercise control. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose information by means of such features, and you agree to assume all responsibility for doing so.

LIMITED DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES

Personal Information about our customers is an integral part of our business. We do not share Personal Information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We reserve the right to share your Personal Information as described below. We retain vendors to perform tasks on our behalf and we may share your Personal Information with them to provide products or services to you. For example, we may need to provide your Personal Information to a third-party credit card processor in order to process a transaction. We will only grant to these vendors the right to use your Personal Information to the limited extent necessary in order to provide the service for which we have retained the vendor. We do not share your Personal Information with our licensees (i.e., companies to which we provide services or technology), unless you decide to upload a resume and you enable your account settings to permit us to share it. In that circumstance, we only share resumes with licensees when criteria we have developed on behalf of such licensees suggest a likelihood that particular users may be a good match for such licensees (i.e., taking into account criteria developed as a result of use of our services). You have the option to set your account settings to ‘Private’ and during periods when your account is identified as such, your Personal Information will not be shared with licensees.

We also disclose Personal Information when required to do so by law, or in response to a subpoena, court order, or other legal mechanism, or when we believe, in our sole discretion, that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of the Company, third parties or the public at large.

We reserve the right to sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of our assets, including your Personal Information and other information provided by you, in connection with a merger, reorganization or sale of some or all of our assets or in the event of bankruptcy. In such event, your Personal Information and other information may be one of the assets transferred. We will post notice before your Personal Information is transferred. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purposes.

IS PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT ME SECURE?

The Site has implemented and maintains reasonable security procedures and practices to protect against the unauthorized access, use, modification, destruction or disclosure of your Personal Information. For example, we use one or more of SSL encryption, firewalls and self-updating anti-virus software. User purchase information is encrypted.

CHOICE

You are not required to register to gain access to many areas of the Site. If you use the Site’s personalized services, however, we will treat your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

MORE ON PRIVACY

Children’s online privacy protection

Pymetrics understands the importance of protecting children’s privacy, especially in an online environment. Accordingly, the Site, the App, and the Software are not designed for or directed at children; the subject matter of the Site and the App is not designed for or directed at children; and the content, including any video or audio, on the Site or the App is not designed for or directed at children. Likewise, it is our policy not to knowingly collect, maintain, use or disclose information about anyone under the age of 13.

Links to third party sites

The Site and the App may contain links to third party websites or mobile applications. The Company neither owns nor controls these third-party websites or mobile applications and accordingly assumes no responsibility for the information practices of those websites or mobile applications. You should inform yourself with the privacy policies (if any) of those third-party websites or mobile applications.

CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time as our services change and grow. We will indicate any such changes at the privacy link at the bottom of our home page or in the settings page. Accordingly, each time you use the Site or the App you should check the “Last Updated” date of this Privacy Policy (located at the top), and review any changes since you last accessed the Site or the App. Such changes are effective ten (10) calendar days after the Last Updated date (the date they become effective is the “effective date”). Unless Company obtains your express consent, any revised Privacy Policy will apply only to information collected after the effective date of such revised Privacy Policy, and not to information collected under any earlier Privacy Policy.

QUESTIONS AND CONCERNS

We welcome inquiries or comments about our Privacy Policy and any queries or concerns about pymetrics by email at help@pymetrics.com. You may also send a letter to the following address:

79 Madison Ave. 2nd Fl. New York, NY 10016
